Guide to the Beverly Coyle Papers, circa 1800-2016 (bulk 1952-2016)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series VIII. Audiovisual Materials
  - Audio Cassettes
    - Beverly Coyle, 1040 AM radio, undated (Box 21)
    - Beverly Coyle, the replay company, undated (Box 21)
    - Dorothy Jones, B. Coyle, 2002 Dec; (90-minute cassette) (Box 21)
    - Bill and Bev, 2004 Jan 8; (90-minute cassette) (Box 21)
    - Loretta, B and J, 2003 Apr 8, 2005; (90-minute cassette) (Box 21)
    - Beverly and Bill, 2002 Dec 14; (60-minute cassette) (Box 21)
    - Jazz Journey Directors, undated; (60-minute cassette) (Box 21)
    - Bev and Laurie, 1968; (90-minute cassette) (Box 21)
    - Bev at Lake Junaluska, 1990 Aug; (90-minute cassette) (Box 21)
    - Pompano Pelican Interview, undated; (90-minute cassette) (Box 21)
    - Untitled, undated; (Two 90-minute cassettes) (Box 21)
    - Coyle – NVP Story, University of Indiana, 1998 Feb; (90-minute cassette) (Box 21)
    - A November tape for Beverly: a recycling program, undated; (90-minute cassette) (Box 21)
    - Black Attitude, Connie does "attitude," Pinewood, 2003 May; (60-minute cassette) (Box 21)
    - Cajon Rest., 1990 Nov 29; (90-minute cassette) (Box 21)
    - The Life You Save May Be Your Own, Flannery O'Connor, undated; (90-minute cassette) (Box 21)
    - In Troubled Waters, WUSF-FM, Tampa, FLA, 1996 May 31; (90-minute cassette) (Box 21)
    - Roseanne Cash Sampler, undated (Box 21)
  - DVDS
    - Power Point Slides B and J Project (Box 21)
    - B and J sound (Box 21)
    - B and J, Empathy, I'm a Liberal, SAVED, Say Yes to War (Box 21)
    - Unidentified, from Jamie (Box 21)
    - B and J crowd (Box 21)
    - Parallel Lives (Box 21)
  - 45 rpm Record
    - The Newcastle Song, Bob Hudson (Box 21)
  - VHS Tapes
    - Unidentified, 1990 Mar 18 (Box 21)
    - Focus on Women with host Florence Rapoport — guest, Beverly Coyle (Box 21)